already houses welcome back and in this video I'm going to show you how to
已经欢迎回来了 视频我将向您展示如何操作
perform calculations on dictionary values rather than the keys if you guys
在字典上执行计算 价值而不是钥匙，如果你们
are like wow that sounds incredibly boring I am probably never going to need
就像听起来令人难以置信的哇 无聊我可能永远 不需要
this check this out let's say that you just out of this
这检查出来 让我们说你就是这个
awesome formula - I don't know like predict the prices of stocks so you have
真棒公式- 我不知道喜欢 预测你所拥有的股票价格
all these stocks and the first thing that you gotta figure out is just what
所有这些股票和第一件事 你 必须 弄明白的是什么
is I don't know like the cheapest stock so you try to do something like this using your programming skills alright
是我不知道最便宜的 股票 所以你尝试做这样的事情 使用你的编程技巧好吧
I'm just going to print min it gives me the minimum value of some sets some data
我只是 要 打印分钟它给了我 某些数据的最小值设置了一些数据
set or iterable so I'll just write stocks right there and it should give me
设置或迭代所以我只会写 股票就在那里它应该给我
the cheapest one wait a minute it said a APL hmm let's look at this right here that's not right see Apple is 325 bucks
最便宜的一款等一下 它说 APL嗯， 让我们来看看这里 这是不对的， 看到苹果是325美元
and the cheapest one looks like Ford so why the heck isn't this working
而最便宜的一款看起来像福特 这样 为什么这不起作用
well it actually did work just not in the way that you thought see by default
以及它实际上做的工作 只是没有在 你 默认 看到的方式
whenever you're running these calculations on a dictionary it's going to look at the key rather than the value
每当你运行这些时 在字典上进行计算 看看关键而 不是价值
so this is the key and this is the value so it did give you the minimum one it's
所以这是关键，这就是价值 所以它确实给你 最小的一个
just that the minimum one in alphabetical order was Apple but that's
只是最小的一个 字母顺序是苹果，但那是
not what we want we want the cheapest one which is Ford so how the heck do we
不是我们想要的最便宜的 一个是福特， 所以我们怎么样
get that long stocks no not let's figure this out all right so we can't just sort
获得那些长期股票不会让我们想象 这很顺利， 所以我们不能只是排序
it the default way or else we don't get what we want what we actually need to do
这是默认的方式，否则我们没有得到 我们想要的是我们 真正需要 做什么
is we actually need to create a new list and we do that by using zip now whenever
我们实际上需要 创建一个新列表 我们现在就通过使用zip来做到这一点
you use it what this is going to do is it's going to return a list of tuples so
你使用它将要做的是 它会返回一个元组列表
what we can essentially do is anytime you have two lists we can essentially
我们基本上可以做的就是随时 你有两个 我们可以基本上的 清单
zip them together so what we're going to do is we're going to get a list of these
把它们拉在一起， 这样我们就会 去 我们是否会 得到这些清单
values and a list of these values and we're going to tie them together so the
值和这些值的列表和 我们要把它们绑在一起这样的
value is first so essentially what we end up is with is something like this
价值首先基本上是我们的 最终是 这样的
instead of goob four three four we end up with four
而不是goob 四个四个四个我们最终有四个
three four gook and then we end up with three to five AAPL there we go so again
三个四个人然后我们结束了 我们再去 三 到五个AAPL
this isn't valid Python but I just want to demonstrate what we're essentially
这不是有效的Python，但我只是想要 证明我们本质上是什么
doing let me just go ahead and comment that so you guys can see all right so
干脆让我继续评论 这样你们就可以看到了
let me just say mint price holy min rice the minimum amount of rice that I can
让我只说薄荷价格圣米饭 我 能吃的最少量的米饭
eat in one day is one pound no less what am I talking about all right let's go
在一天吃是 一磅 不少于什么 我说的很好， 我们走吧
ahead and keep going art so we're getting the minimum still we're going to get the minimum value but instead of
领先并继续前进艺术， 所以我们 得到最低限度仍然是我们要去的 得到最小值但不是
just throwing our dictionary in there before because that's just going to sort
只是把我们的字典扔在那里 之前， 因为那只是要排序
by the keys what we're going to do is this we're going to zip two values
通过钥匙，我们要做的是 这个我们要压缩两个值
together now what values do you want is it together or the first one is just
现在， 你 想要的是什么价值观 它同时还是第一个就是
going to be the values so how do we get that we just read stocks values easiest thing ever
将成为价值观，我们如何得到 我们只是阅读最简单的股票价值 事情永远
now the second one is going to give us stocks keys so all we're doing right
现在第二个将给我们 库存钥匙所以我们所做的一切都是 正确的
here is instead of having the keys first in the value second all we're saying is
这里 不是先把钥匙拿出来 在 我们所说的 第二个价值 中
put the values first in the key second easiest thing you've probably ever done in your life and now let me just print
将值放在第二个键中 你可能做过的最简单的事情 在你的生活中 ， 现在让我打印
out what we found so print out mint price and there you go all right so what
我们发现了什么， 所以 打印薄荷 价格，那你 就没事 了
we did is we now reorganize that essentially that's all we did and we
我们所做的是我们现在重新组织 基本上就是我们所做的一切，我们
print out the minimum which is indeed forward so there you go that ladies and gentlemen is how you perform custom
打印出的最低这 确实是 所以 你去那个女士们 先生们是你如何 执行习俗
dictionary calculations on the values rather than the keys you can go make
值的 字典计算 而不是你可以做的钥匙
millions with your incredible awesome stock formula now I'm going to keep
数百万人拥有令人难以置信的超棒 库存配方现在我要保留
making videos so I'll see you guys next time
制作影片，让我来看看你们 未来 时间